Daniel Gonzalez

Graphic Designer

Los Angeles, CA 90013 dannyygonzalez95@yahoo.com +1 626 315 8141

Driven by creativity, and dedicated to deliver unprecedented content, I am prepared to provide my professional skillsets for my next venture. I hold over 6 years of experience in Graphic Design, Web Development, Photography, and Videography. I am highly proficient with photoshop, illustrator, and Dreamweaver. I shoot all of my photos and videos on my Sony A7S III, and edit my video content on Premiere Pro. On top of creativity, I have experience building responsive websites utilizing HTML, CSS, and Javascript.

Below is my design portfolio:

Design: https://dannygnzdesigns.jimdofree.com/

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Graphic Designer

Filmtools - Burbank, CA September 2019 to Present

- Design graphics for the website, digital advertisements, & marketing campaigns
- Create designs for physical prints: Packaging, postcards, banners, and wraps
- Create fluid & responsive web wireframes
- Build out campaign landing pages
- Shoot both marketing & product photos
- Retouch photos
- Curate & design weekly newsletters
- · Create logos for new campaigns

Web Content Specialist

Samy's Camera - Los Angeles, CA December 2014 to September 2019

- Add new products with detailed images and copy
- Edit product photos
- Create banners for web pages, emails, and social media
- Improve SEO based on gathered data
- Integrate up-sell and cross-sell items per product
- Improve search result compatibility

Education

Bachelor of Arts in Graphic Design

California State University-Dominguez Hills - Carson, CA August 2017 to May 2019

Skills

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- · Graphic design
- Web design
- HTML5
- JavaScript
- CSS

Links

https://dannygnzdesigns.jimdofree.com/

Assessments

Search engine optimization — Highly Proficient

August 2021

Interpreting online website performance metrics and understanding search engine optimization tactics Full results: <u>Highly Proficient</u>

Work style: Reliability — Expert

September 2021

Tendency to be reliable, dependable, and act with integrity at work

Full results: Expert

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.